The silver shoes had fallen off in her flight to the air and were lost forever
in the desert.
End of Chapter 23.
This is a librivox recording. All librivox recordings are in the public
domain. For more information or to volunteer, please visit librivox.org. This
recording by Jay Hall.
The Wonderful Wizard of Oz by L. Frank Baum. Chapter 24: Home Again. Aunt Em had
just come out of the house to water the cabbages when she looked up and saw
Dorothy running toward her. "My darling child!" she cried, folding the little girl
in her arms and covering her face with kisses. "Where in the world did you come from?"
"From the Land of Oz," said Dorothy gravely,
"and here is Toto too. Oh, Aunt Em, I am so
glad to be home again!" End of The Wonderful Wizard of Oz by L. Frank Baum.